The Rats: A Witcher Tale is a fantasy, drama,
adventure film directed by Mairzee Almas.
To pull off a daring heist, a gang of six misfit outlaws will have to do something
they've never done before: trust each other — and a washed-up Witcher.
Mistle, played by Christelle Elwin.
Giselher, played by Ben Radcliffe.
Kayleigh, played by Fabian McCallum.
Iskra, played by Aggy K. Adams.
Asse, played by Connor Crawford.
Reef, played by Juliette Alexandra.
The Witcher is a fantasy drama television series created
by Lauren Schmidt Hissrich for Netflix.
It is based on the book series by Polish author Andrzej Sapkowski.
Set on a fictional, medieval-inspired landmass known as the Continent, The Witcher explores
the legend of Geralt of Rivia, Yennefer of Vengerberg, and Princess Ciri.
It stars Henry Cavill and Liam Hemsworth as Geralt,
with Anya Chalotra and Freya Allan.
The first season, consisting of eight episodes, was released on Netflix
on December 20, 2019, starring Cavill in the lead role.
It was based on The Last Wish and Sword of Destiny, which are collections
of short stories that precede the main The Witcher saga.
The second season, also consisting of eight episodes and based on the
novel Blood of Elves, was released on December 17, 2021.
The third season, which also consists of eight episodes and is based on the novel Time
of Contempt, was released in two volumes on June 29 and July 27, 2023.
Hemsworth took over the role of Geralt of Rivia in the fourth season, based on the novel
Baptism of Fire, which was released on October 30, 2025, also with eight episodes.
In April 2024, the series was renewed for its fifth and final season.
An animated origin story film, Nightmare of the
Wolf, was released on August 23, 2021.
A prequel miniseries, Blood Origin, was released on December 25, 2022.
A second animated film, Sirens of the Deep, was released on February 11, 2025.
A feature-length special, The Rats: A Witcher Tale,
was released on October 30, 2025.
The film explores themes of witch, monster, based
on novel or book, magic, mutant.
The tone is dark and emotional.